ILGWU. Susan Cowell papers, 5780/097
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Starobin, Harold. Miscellaneous, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- ILG Participation, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- American Family Celebration Day. Stage and Sound, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- American Family Celebration Day. Logistics, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- American Family Celebration Day. Transportation, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- American Family Celebration Day. Exhibit Booths, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- American Family Day Celebration. Invitations, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- American Family Day Celebration. Program, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- American Family Day Celebration. Foundations, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- American Family Day Celebration. Speaker Invitations, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- American Family Day Celebration. Contributions, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Solidarity Day. Demonstrations, 1983-1987 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Resumes, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- CLUW Chapters, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- CLC's, State Federations, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Union Outreach, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Outreach, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Endorsements, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- February Tenth Meeting, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  February, tenth
- Lists, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Press Release American Family Celebration, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Press Conference, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Literature, Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Spanish; Chinese
- Family Bill of Rights, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Mobilization, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Petition/Political Action, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Press May Fourteenth [folder1 of 2], 1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Press May Fourteenth [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Family Stories, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Labor Press American Family Celebration [folder1 of 2], 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Labor Press American Family Celebration [folder 2 of 2], 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- May Fourteenth Follow Up, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- May Fourteenth American Family Celebration- General, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- New York City Organizing Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Women's Groups, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Churches, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Child Care Groups, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Expenses- Budget, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Updates, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- National Coordinating Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- 5 Industries Press, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Academic Analysis, homework, 1986-1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Airlie House Conference, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- American Association of Retired Persons (AARP), article and responses, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- American Home Sewing, 1986-1991 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Bourdeaux, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Canada, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Case Studies, 1986-2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Chicago Hearings, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Clerical Homework, 1986-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Clinton, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Congress, correspondence, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Congress, correspondence, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Dallas, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Department of Labor, Advance Notice Women's Apparel, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Department of Labor, internal debate, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Department of Labor, proposal, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Department of Labor, 5 industries, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Enforcement Issues, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Expenses, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Facts (Box 10, Folder 21)
  no date
- Final Rule, 5 industries, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Fires, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- General information requests, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Gesell decision, December, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Hearings, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Hearings, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Homework Coalition, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Homework Coalition, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Homework Fact Sheets, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Industrial Homework, background, 1941-1990 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- International, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- International Labor Organization (ILO), 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- International Ladies Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU) Campaign, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Campaign, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Campaign, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Campaign, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- ILGWU, statements and comments, 1981-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Investigations, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Jewelry, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Knitted Outerwear, 1981-1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles Hearings, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Maine and North Carolina Hearings, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Miami Hearings, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Michael Sheehan Media Training, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous support letters, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- New York City Council, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- New York City Hearings, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- New York Times Advertisement, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- North American Precise, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration, Homework, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Pieces, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Photos, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Press clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Press relations, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Press relations, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Press, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- San Antonio Hearings, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Suits, 5 industries, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Testimonies, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Women's Apparel, homework, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- written comments, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Blue Cross, rate increase, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Bus tour (Health Security Express), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- California Initiative, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Campaign for Health Security, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Campaign for Health Security, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Canada (Healthcare), 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Clinton, healthcare, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Clinton, plan slides, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Clinton plan, summaries, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Clinton plan, reaction, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Emergency drive (for healthcare reform), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Strategies, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Events (healthcare), April, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, February, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Expenditures (Healthcare Reform Fund), 1994 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Final analysis (defeat of Clinton's healthcare security act), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Gottfried Bill, A8912 (single-payer care bill), New York State, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Healthcare, 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Healthcare Reform Project, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Healthcare Task Force, AFL-CIO, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Healthcare Union, miscellaneous, 1990-1994 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- International (healthcare), 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- ILGWU, early retiree, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- ILGWU, Healthcare Campaign, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- ILGWU, Healthcare Grassroots Task Force, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- ILGWU, Healthcare, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- ILGWU, member mailing, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- ILGWU, small businesses and healthcare reform, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Jobs with Justice Fundraiser, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Mitchell, George J. (Senate Majority Leader); Kennedy, Edward (Senator), 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- New York City Jobs with Justice (healthcare campaign), 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- New York City Jobs with Justice (healthcare campaign), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- New York City, small businesses (healthcare reform), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- New York Times Advertisements (healthcare), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- other federal bills (healthcare), 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Post Executive Council, AFL-CIO, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Rally, July 11, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Roll Call advertisements, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Screen Actors Guild Fund (fund for health security), 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Single-payer group, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Single-payer strategy debate, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Single-payer, Russo, Marty (representative), 1991 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Small businesses, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- State bills, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Survey data, healthcare, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- White House post-card delivery, March 23; White House and healthcare, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Adolfo, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Bill drafts, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- California Joint Liability, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- California Registration Bill, 1979-1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- California Testimony, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- California, other (Concentrated Enforcement Program), 1978-1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Compliance Agreement, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Federal enforcement, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Garment Industry Job Retention Act, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- General Accounting Office, Schumer Bill, 1987-1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- General media and exposes, 1987-1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Industry lobbying, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Kong case, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Legislation (sweatshops), 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Montoya visit to Queens, New York (State Senator Joseph Montoya of California), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- New Jersey, 1984-1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- New York State Bills, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- New York State Enforcement Unit, 1983-1992 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- New York State Labor Department Staffing and Funding, 1983-1988 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Photos (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Policy statements and press releases, 1979-1988 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Proposals for expanding fashion industry (New York and New Jersey) (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Registration bill (New York State), 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Roseking/Rainbow/Frances Wang, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- San Francisco Master Agreement, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Sweatshop Bill, New York State, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Teammate Fashions, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Ad campaign, Local 17-18, United Production Workers Union, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Advertising Contract, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Affiliation with ILGWU, Local 17-18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Background, violations, government assistance (Local 17-18), 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn, New York, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Bus posters (ILGWU), 1983-1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Campaign brochure (Campaign for Justice), 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Campaign for Justice, 1989-1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Campaign for Justice, press, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Choice, AFL-CIO, abortion and other reproductive rights, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Choice, AFL-CIO, press, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Choice, Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Choice, ILGWU, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Choice, other, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Churches, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Coalitions, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Cuomo, Mario (Governor of New York), 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Dinner, Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Dinner, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Dinner, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Dinner, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Dinner, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Disability Insurance. Temporary disability insurance, 1986-1995 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Domsey Charges miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- E. Williamsburg Judicial Development, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- El Paso, DCB INC., 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- El Paso, press, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Elections, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Enforcement (use of union labels), 1983-1992 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Fact sheets (Campaign for Justice, Brooklyn) (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Foundations, Chung Pak Child Care Center, Child Care Grant Project, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- General, Local 17-18, 1990-1994 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Guiliani, Rudolph, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Healthcare television advertisement, ILGWU, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- ILGWU, chorus, 1989-1996 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- ILGWU, contracts, parental leave, 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- ILGWU, organizing, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Isratex, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Jackson, Jesse Rally, July 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Norma Kamali, INC., 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Label, legal issues, 1982-1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Labor support, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Lobbying, Family and Medical Leave Act, 1987-1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, 1989-1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Mademoiselle Knitwear, INC., 1990-1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Malcolm Dodds Music, INC., 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Mayor Dinkins, David, 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Metropolitan Fashion Center, Brooklyn Army Terminal, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Miami, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous, international solidarity, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Miss America advertisement, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Morris Survey, union label, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- New Jersey Parental Leave Bill, 1986-1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- New York City Council, 1989-1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- New York City Elections, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- New York State parental/disability leave, 1982-1992 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Organizing and field services, 1983-1991 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Other advertising, ILGWU, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Parental Leave, 1984-1996 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Permission to use advertisement/song (Look for the Union Label), 1980-1997 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Children's Village, 1981-1984 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Presidential, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Press coverage, Labor Day parades, 1983-1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Rag trade, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Rally, May 31, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Salvation Army et al, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- San Francisco, 1990-1994 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Soho, 1988-1992 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Soho, press, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Spanish radio advertisements, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Sunset Park, Chinatown, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Swanknit, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Task Force Organizing, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Puente, Tito, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Union label advertisements and background, 1977-1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Union label advertisements, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Union label advertisements, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Union label bridal promotion, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Union Label Department, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Voter Registration, 1984-1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Williamsburg Trade Association Campaign, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Women's Wear Daily advertisements, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Work release, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Worker's Center (275 7th Avenue), 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Agency for Child Development, contract with Chinese American Planning Council, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Agency for Child Development, contracts, 1983-1995 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Andmore Sportswear, Port Jerris Child Care, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Board, Day Care Center, 1984-1999 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Board, budget, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Chinatown, survey, Day Care Center, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Chung Pak Child Care Fund, financial statements, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Chung Pak Child Care Fund, financial statements, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Chung Pak, legal documents, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Chung Pak, opening, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Donors, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown, financial statements, 1985-1993 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown, creation of, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Garment Industry Day Care Survey Committee, Day Care Council, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Grants, Day Care Center, 1986-1994 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Incorporation of Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown and bylaws, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Liz Claiborne and day care, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Operation, day care center, 1983-1992 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- press coverage, center, 1983-1993 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Airlie Conference, April, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Women's Department, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1988-2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Government's Task Force on Work and Family, 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Institute for Women and Work, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Institute for Women's Policy Research, 1987-1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- National Council of Jewish Women, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- New York City Commission on the Status of Women, 1977-1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- New York Women's Agenda, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Radcliffe Conference, May 1995 and April 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Take Your Daughters to Work, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Union bargaining, family issues, 1987-1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Wider Opportunities for Women, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Women and Unions, 1986-1998 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Women in the Workplace, 1989-1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Work in America Institute, December, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Child Care Action Campaign, 1984-1992 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Child Care Action Campaign, D.C. fundraiser, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Child Care Action Campaign, union fundraising, 1989-1996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Child Care Project, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Consortium for Worker Education, child care, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Day Care and unions, 1981-1992 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation Child Care Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- ILGWU and Child Care, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- ILGWU, work and family, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- New York City Labor Child Care Coalition, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- New York City Temporary Commission, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- New York State Child Care Commission, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Union of Needletrades Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE), child care, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Klein, Adam, 1990-1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- advertising, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Angelo, Alfred, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- auditing, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Boycott/Rally, Lesile Fay, etc., 1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Buttons/letterhead, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Communications Task Force, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Communications Task Force, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Communications Task Force, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Contract benefits, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Contract language, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Contract language, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Contract, press, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Contract, public relations, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Contract, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Dues increase, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Facts, negotiations, 1988-1994 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Industry Promotion Funds, 1986-1994 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Internal organizing, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- International Organizing and Solidarity, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- ILGWU, contracts (general), 1972-1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- ILGWU Task Forces, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Joint ILGWU and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, contract, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Justice (Spanish), 1988 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Leslie Faye, 1992-1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Leslie Fay, press, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Louis Hornick and Company, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Maiden Form, 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Major market negotiations, 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Member benefits survey, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Negotiations, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Negotiations, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Organizing policy, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Outreach, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Political support, hearings, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Press, negotiation, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Public relations/fact sheets, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Public relations, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Settlement, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Trade Federation Enclosures, 1985-1988 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- United in 1994 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Video, Leslie Fay, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Warehouse contracts, 1985-1988 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Warehouse Task Force, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- We Are One, materials, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Background (child labor), 1989-1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Federal (child labor), 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Federal bills (child labor), 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- General Accounting Office, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Health and Safety, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- International child labor, 1990-1995 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- ILGWU, testimonies, 1989-1998 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- New York State Child Labor Advisory Group, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Press, child labor, 1988-1997 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO, immigration, 1987-1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Background, immigration, 1986-1995 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Discrimination, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Employer sanctions, 1987-1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- General Accounting Office, report and sanctions, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Haitians, 1984-1993 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Immigration bill, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Immigration law, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Immigration Project, 23-25, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Immigration Task Force, 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- ILGWU statements, 1980-1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- ILGWU and immigrant history (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Labor and Employer Sanctions, 1987-1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement and Employer Sanctions, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Legal cases, 1986-1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Legalization celebration, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Los Angeles Immigration Project, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- National Immigration Project, 1984-1991 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- New York Times, op-ed, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- New York Times, op-ed, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Post International Control and Reform Act Policy, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Press, ILGWU, 1987-1993 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Shop raids, Delgado, 1979-1989 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Temporary Workers, H-2 Visa, 1981-1992 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Winnie Fashions, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Section 936 (Internal Revenue Code), Puerto Rico, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Agency for International Development, expose, 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO, China, notes, 1989-1992 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Central America, 1985-1990 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- China, 1989-2000 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Crafted with Pride, 1985-1992 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Damon Dress, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Gephardt Meeting, December, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Import Activities, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Import Activities, Spring, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Import Bill, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Imports, Canada, 1985-1990 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Imports, Chinatown, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Imports (rollback), 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- International Labor Organization, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- International Labor Solidarity, 1988-1997 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- ILGWU and international relations, 1984-1993 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- ILGWU campaign, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- ILGWU, North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) Campaign, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- ILGWU, on trade policy, 1985-1992 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- ILGWU, South Africa, 1984-1991 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- International Textiles, Garment, and Leather Workers Federation, 1987-1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Iraq War, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Israel, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Japan, 1986-1994 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Ramirez, Jose, tour (trip to New York City), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Korea, 1987-1997 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Label law, buy American, 1984-1995 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Labor and international, 1985-2000 (Box 22, Folder 11)